Henry F. Dobyns Papers 1732-2009 (bulk 1950-2000)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series XI: Photographic Material, 1932-2000
  - Subseries 3: Negatives, 1942-1988
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 475, Folder 25)
  - Subseries 4: Slides, 1948-1985
    This subseries contains personal images as well as slides relating to research in Latin American countries and work with Indian Tribes. Boxes 476-480. This subseries contains restrictions on materials in box 477 folder 9-12.
    - Aerial views, 1967 (Box 476, Folder 1)
    - Archaeology lecture, 1963 (Box 476, Folder 2)
    - Baboquivari, undated (Box 476, Folder 3)
    - Balboa Park, 1968 (Box 476, Folder 4)
    - Bolivia, 1964-1965 (Box 476, Folder 5-11)
    - Bolivia- Colquiri, 1965 (Box 476, Folder 12)
    - Bolivia- Sabaya, 1965 (Box 476, Folder 13)
    - Bolivia- Tahua, 1965 (Box 476, Folder 14)
    - Cacti, 1948-1952, 1985 (Box 476, Folder 15)
    - Colorado River Reservation, 1949-1956 (Box 476, Folder 16)
    - Conference Meetings, 1949-1968 (Box 476, Folder 17)
    - Cornell University and Ithaca, New York, 1955-1965 (Box 476, Folder 18)
    - Dams, undated (Box 476, Folder 19)
    - Desert Landscapes, undated (Box 476, Folder 20)
    - Ecuador, 1963-1964 (Box 477, Folder 1)
    - Ecuador, 1964-1965 (Box 477, Folder 2)
    - Ecuador, 1968 (Box 477, Folder 3)
    - Ecuador-Kentucky Partners of the Alliance Trip, 1965 (Box 477, Folder 4)
    - Family, 1963-1972 (Box 477, Folder 5)
    - Fort Apache Indian Reservation, 1971 (Box 477, Folder 6)
    - Gila River Indian Reservation, 1948-1985 (Box 477, Folder 7)
    - Hermosillo, Mexico, 1974 (Box 477, Folder 8)
    - Restricted (Box 477, Folder 9-11)
    - Restricted (Box 477, Folder 12)
    - Indiana University Bloomington Anthropology department, 1968 (Box 477, Folder 13)
    - Kennedy Airport Aircraft Storm Landing, 1967 (Box 477, Folder 14)
    - Magdalena, Sonora, Mexico, 1949-1960 (Box 477, Folder 15-17)
    - Magdalena, Sonora, Mexico, 1970 (Box 477, Folder 18)
    - Magdalena, Sonora, Mexico, 1971-1973 (Box 477, Folder 19)
    - Maps and graphs, undated (Box 477, Folder 20)
    - Mexico, undated (Box 477, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 1948-1975 (Box 477, Folder 22)
    - New Mexico, undated (Box 478, Folder 1)
    - New Mexico Papago, 1948-1951 (Box 478, Folder 2)
    - Northern Arizona, 1962-1972 (Box 478, Folder 3)
    - Peace Corps training, 1962 (Box 478, Folder 4)
    - Peru, 1960-1965 (Box 478, Folder 5-7)
    - Peru, 1967-1970 (Box 478, Folder 8-9)
    - Peru- Aerials, 1964-1965 (Box 478, Folder 10)
    - Peru- Archaeology, 1960-1964 (Box 478, Folder 11)
    - Peru- Coastal Valleys, 1960-1964 (Box 478, Folder 12)
    - Peru- Folk dances, 1964 (Box 478, Folder 13)
    - Peru- Huaylas, 1960 (Box 478, Folder 14)
    - Peru- Lima flights, 1965-1967 (Box 478, Folder 15)
    - Peru- Mayobamba- Dr. Monge visit, undated (Box 478, Folder 16)
    - Peru- Mayobamba- Rio Santa RR, 1960 (Box 478, Folder 17)
    - Peru- Plazas, 1960-1968 (Box 478, Folder 18)
    - Peru- Vicos, 1960-1965 (Box 478, Folder 19)
    - Plants, 1980 (Box 478, Folder 20)
    - Pots, undated (Box 478, Folder 21)
    - Prescott, Arizona, 1970-1972 (Box 478, Folder 22)
    - Printed Images, undated (Box 479, Folder 1-4)
    - Puerto Rico, 1964 (Box 479, Folder 5-6)
    - Queen Valley, Arizona, undated (Box 479, Folder 7)
    - San Carlos Apache Reservation, 1950 (Box 479, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco Xavier del Bac, 1957, 1975 (Box 479, Folder 9)
    - Sells, Arizona, 1973 (Box 479, Folder 10)
    - Sells Rodeo, 1972 (Box 479, Folder 11)
    - Society for Applied Anthropology meeting- Mexico City, 1969 (Box 479, Folder 12)
    - Sonora, Mexico, 1952-1974 (Box 479, Folder 13)
    - South America, undated (Box 479, Folder 14)
    - Southwest Indians, 1948-1952 (Box 479, Folder 15)
    - Southwest and Mexico, 1948-1952 (Box 479, Folder 16-17)
    - Texas, 1972, 1975 (Box 479, Folder 18)
    - Tohono O’odham, 1948-1952 (Box 479, Folder 19-20)
    - Twweep petroglyphs, 1972 (Box 479, Folder 21)
    - Unidentified, 1980, undated (Box 479, Folder 22)
    - University of Arizona, 1956 (Box 479, Folder 23)
    - University of Kentucky, 1966-1971 (Box 480, Folder 1)
    - US Travel, 1950-1952 (Box 480, Folder 2)
    - US Travel, 1962-1975 (Box 480, Folder 3-6)
    - Venezuela, 1976 (Box 480, Folder 7)
    - We told you so... But you just were not listening, 1949-1971 (Box 480, Folder 8)
    - W.H. Emory Boundary Survey Plates, undated (Box 480, Folder 9)
    - Wildflowers and birds, 1968-1973 (Box 480, Folder 10)
    - Xochmilco, Mexico City, 1968-1969 (Box 480, Folder 11)
- Series XII: Audiovisual Material, 1937-2001
  This series contains audiovisual material related to research of the Hualapai, Tohono O’odham and Peru research as well as drafts of writings. It is divided into three subseries. This series contains restrictions on material in box 481 folders 1-14, 16-32, 46-47, 51 and box 482 folder 4-6, 8-10, 11-14, 16, 19-20, 24.
  - Subseries 1: Audio and video recordings, 1937-1978
    This subseries contains recordings of interviews related to the Hualapai, Tohono O’odham and research in Peru as well as various other events. It is arranged chronologically. Some access copies are available. Box 481-482. This series contains restrictions on material in box 481 folders 1-14, 16-32, 46-47, 51 and box 482 folder 4-6, 8-10, 11-14, 16, 19-20, 24.
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 1)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 2)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 3)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 4-6)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 7)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 8)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 9)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 10-11)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 12)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 13)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 14)
    - Indiana anthro presentation 5/31/55, 1955 (Box 481, Folder 15)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 16)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 17)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 18-19)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 20)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 21)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 22)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 23)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 24)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 25)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 26)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 27)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 28)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 29)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 30)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 31)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 32)
    - Neff, Jerry, Peace Corps Volunteer account of Chimbote experience, 1964 (Box 481, Folder 33)
    - Presentation of Anthropology club, 1967 (Box 481, Folder 34)
    - Mariachis, Magdalena, Sonora Mexico, 1971 (Box 481, Folder 35)
    - Bolivia- Burela, undated (Box 481, Folder 36-45)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 46)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 47)
    - Brown French lesson 2 parts 1 and 2, undated (Box 481, Folder 48)
    - Carcas school singing, undated (Box 481, Folder 49)
    - Congo drums, undated (Box 481, Folder 50)
    - Restricted (Box 481, Folder 51)
    - Dictation tape 104-10, undated (Box 481, Folder 52)
    - Dictation tape- no markings, undated (Box 481, Folder 53)
    - Dictation tape- to 124, undated (Box 481, Folder 54)
    - Dictation tape- to 129, undated (Box 481, Folder 55)
    - Dictation tape- Boxes 40-53, undated (Box 481, Folder 56)
    - Discussion of Maricopa County politics, undated (Box 482, Folder 1)
    - Dobyns giving advice to author/student re work in Ecuador, undated (Box 482, Folder 2)
    - Ecuador Indian people film narration “Our Lives”, undated (Box 482, Folder 3)
    - Restricted (Box 482, Folder 4-5)
    - Restricted (Box 482, Folder 6)
    - Henry Dobyns #1, undated (Box 482, Folder 7)
    - Restricted (Box 482, Folder 8-9)
    - Restricted (Box 482, Folder 10)
    - Restricted (Box 482, Folder 11-13)
    - Restricted (Box 482, Folder 14)
    - “Merry Christmas Cara Beth”, 16 mm home movie, 1937 (Box 482, Folder 15)
    - Restricted (Box 482, Folder 16)
    - Narration while in moving vehicle, undated (Box 482, Folder 17)
    - Native American Language speaking lessons, undated (Box 482, Folder 18)
    - Restricted (Box 482, Folder 19)
    - Restricted (Box 482, Folder 20)
    - Possibly South American, 16 mm silent color film, undated (Box 482, Folder 21)
    - Sale of Chancos (Peru), R. Roberts interviewed by Paul L Doughty, undated (Box 482, Folder 22)
    - Side 2 Dialogue, undated (Box 482, Folder 23)
    - Restricted (Box 482, Folder 24)
    - 84-97 C-1 8, undated (Box 482, Folder 25)
    - 74-83 C-2 9, undated (Box 482, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 2: Computer disks, 1989-2001
    This subseries contains computer floppy disks (3.5 inch) primarily containing drafts of manuscripts as well as some correspondence. It is arranged alphabetically. Box 483.
    - 16th Century Tusayan- Chronology revisions, 1990 (Box 483, Folder 1)
    - Anthology duplicate 15 December, 1991 (Box 483, Folder 2)
    - Arizona newspapers 14 October, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 3)
    - Arizona newspapers issues consulted/noted, undated (Box 483, Folder 4)
    - Arizona Battles 10 October, 1992 (Box 483, Folder 5)
    - AZ Battles 2- Arizona Battles Tables 12 January, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 6)
    - AZ W1-20300 17 May, 2000 (Box 483, Folder 7)
    - Battle AZ text 11 December, 1995 (Box 483, Folder 8)
    - Battles Tables 11 December, 1995 (Box 483, Folder 9)
    - Bills to Office of Water Rights, Gila River Indian Community 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 10)
    - Borderlands 8 May, 2000 (Box 483, Folder 11)
    - Casa Grande History 6 May 1991 on SE women (Box 483, Folder 12)
    - Casa Grande in Tucson, undated (Box 483, Folder 13)
    - Chelsea P-M Integration 17 February, 1989 (Box 483, Folder 14)
    - Chelsea P-M Mysterious 15 February, 1989 (Box 483, Folder 15)
    - Cherum and letters 4 June, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 16)
    - Chiefs, 1997 (Box 483, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence 4 May, 1989 (Box 483, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence- Maritha, Thomas BK, IRS, Best of Books, 1997 (Box 483, Folder 19)
    - Cox & Cox bills, 1990-1995 (Box 483, Folder 20)
    - Cox & Cox bills back up, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 21)
    - Cox & Cox GRIC billing 1/1, 1990 (Box 483, Folder 22)
    - Create GRIR Expand, undated (Box 483, Folder 23)
    - Creation and Expansion of Gila River Indian Reservation 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 24)
    - Creation and Expansion GRIR 11 October, 2000 (Box 483, Folder 25)
    - Dobyns CV, undated (Box 483, Folder 26-27)
    - Dobyns files 30 May, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 28)
    - Dobyns manuscripts, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 29)
    - Dobyns MS 17 November, 1997 (Box 483, Folder 30)
    - Dobyns personal 5 June, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 31)
    - Dobyns review of Smoldering, undated (Box 483, Folder 32)
    - Essays for GRIC-OWR, Dudley comment, Dozen Pima Starving Years, GRIR Toll, SRP buckeye- Arlington comment Salt River, undated (Box 483, Folder 33)
    - Ethnohistory Perspectives, undated (Box 483, Folder 34)
    - Euler Festschrift 20 march, 2001 (Box 483, Folder 35)
    - Flood- Supplement 22 January, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 36)
    - Floods 1: title, 1000-1878, 1879-1984, 5 January, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 37)
    - Floods 2: 1923-1928, 1929-1937, 5 January, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 38)
    - Floods 3: 1897-1911, 1912-1922, 13 February, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 39)
    - Floods 4: 1938-1942, 1943-1952, 20 February, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 40)
    - Floods 5: 1952-1964, 1965-1972, 20 February, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 41)
    - Floods 6: 1973-1977, 1978-1983, 1984-1987, 1988-1993, 20 February, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 42)
    - Floods 7: 1885-1891, 1892-1897, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 43)
    - Floods 8 1912-1916, 1917-1922 26 April, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 44)
    - Floods in the Gila-Salt River Watershed & Droughts 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 45)
    - Floods in the Gila Salt River Watershed & Droughts in neighboring areas, undated (Box 483, Folder 46)
    - Gila River Floods/Droughts 1 August, 1997 (Box 483, Folder 47)
    - Gila River Valley four populations compared 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 48)
    - Gila- Salt River Floods Disk 1, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 49)
    - Gila- Salt River Floods Disk 2, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 50)
    - Globe Equity 59 9 March, 1989 (Box 483, Folder 51)
    - Globe Equity 59- Case History 30 January, 1991 (Box 483, Folder 52)
    - Globe Equity 59 Case History back up, undated (Box 483, Folder 53)
    - Globe Equity 59- Tribs 28 March 1996 Gila River Perennial Tributaries, Hill vs Herrick Index (Box 483, Folder 54)
    - GRIC diabetes 25 June, 2000 (Box 483, Folder 55)
    - GRIC Litigation reports requested 2nd half, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 56)
    - GRIC Reports requested by T.A.J. Gookin on schedule bibliography 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 57)
    - GRIR Claims 30 May 1990 (Box 483, Folder 58)
    - GRIR experiment station 23 April, 1990 (Box 483, Folder 59)
    - GRIR- HSR comment 17 April, 1997 (Box 483, Folder 60)
    - GRIR Salt River 18 February, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 61)
    - HSR-Globe Equity 59 History of the Case 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 62)
    - HSR-GRIR-1,2,3,4,5,Ap 29 December, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 63)
    - Indian Almanac- Demography, Tellman critique, undated (Box 483, Folder 64)
    - Indian author novels: criticism 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 65)
    - Indian Claims Commission docket 236 C and D- Analytical monograph 20 June, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 66)
    - Indian Claims Commission docket 236 reanalysis, 1997 (Box 483, Folder 67)
    - Lawana (Trout) Kinder books 20 February, 1993 (Box 483, Folder 68)
    - Los Tres Alamos: Duplicates 1 May, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 69)
    - Manuscripts 31 May, 1994 (Box 483, Folder 70)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 483, Folder 71)
    - My MS- HF Dobyns manuscripts, colonial climate, dams, riverscape 1 & 2, Blackwater, Pima notes 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 72)
    - Mystery novel, plants, 20 October, 1999 (Box 483, Folder 73)
    - Mystery plants, undated (Box 483, Folder 74)
    - Native Demographics 6 march, 1990 (Box 483, Folder 75)
    - NAU Chapters 1-5, undated (Box 483, Folder 76)
    - NAU Chapter 7-10, undated (Box 483, Folder 77)
    - New American Race 10 August, 1997 (Box 483, Folder 78)
    - Numbers from Nowhere 2 November, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 79)
    - Oacpicagigua 17 June, 1993 (Box 483, Folder 80)
    - Pai Patriot Cherum May, 2000 (Box 483, Folder 81)
    - Pima-Maricopa Confederation Military Service, undated (Box 483, Folder 82)
    - Pima-Maricopa Economic opportunity 12 December, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 83)
    - Pima-Maricopa History 3 September, 1999 (Box 483, Folder 84)
    - Pima- Maricopa Irrigation of Middle Gila River Oasis 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 85)
    - Pima-Maricopa Military Service, 1990 (Box 483, Folder 86)
    - Pima-Maricopa Response to Economic Opportunity & Disincentives 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 87)
    - Pima-Maricopa Salt River Utilization 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 88)
    - Pima Papers backup March 5, 1991 (Box 483, Folder 89)
    - Piman Essays 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 90)
    - Quantifications of Fiction 9 February, 1989 (Box 483, Folder 91)
    - “Re analysis” 22 June 1998, Pima- Maricopa Irrigation of Middle Gila River Oasis (Box 483, Folder 92)
    - References for Creation and Expansion of Gila River Indian Reservation, undated (Box 483, Folder 93)
    - San Carlos Indian Irrigation Project 16 May, 1995 (Box 483, Folder 94)
    - San Carlos Indian Irrigation Project 18 September, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 95)
    - Team Stoffle Manuscripts 14 November, 1998 (Box 483, Folder 96)
    - Trade centers as Disease Foci 30 October 1989, Trade centers, Pima-Goshute, markets, Pueblo-Caddo, Pacific-Colorado (Box 483, Folder 97)
    - Trade Pueblo Market 24 October, 1989 (Box 483, Folder 98)
    - Trade: Pueblo Market & N-2, undated (Box 483, Folder 99)
    - Trade revisions 7 October, 1990 (Box 483, Folder 100)
    - Trade 1- Back up 5 March, 1991 (Box 483, Folder 101)
    - Trade 2 Back-up 5 March, 1991 (Box 483, Folder 102)
    - Trout correspondence, 1999 (Box 483, Folder 103)
    - Tubac Epilogue, undated (Box 483, Folder 104)
    - Tubac through Four Centuries, undated (Box 483, Folder 105-106)
    - Tubac through Four Centuries Epilogue, undated (Box 483, Folder 107)
    - Tusayan Implosion, undated (Box 483, Folder 108)
    - Unreal Speeches Trout-Dobyns MS 14 November, 1996 (Box 483, Folder 109)
    - WP (Walapai People?) Chapters 1-5, undated (Box 483, Folder 110)
    - WP (Walapai People?) Chapter 6, undated (Box 483, Folder 111)
    - WP (Walapai People?) Chapters 7-10, undated (Box 483, Folder 112)
  - Subseries 3: Microfilm, undated
    This subseries contains copies primarily of archival documents from foreign archives including Mexican and Spanish archives. Box 484.
    - Archivo General de Indias, Audiencia de Guadalajara 135, Reels 79, 85, 88, 97, 98, 99; 137 Reels 138, 139, 140, 141, 142, 143, undated (Box 484, Folder 1)
    - Archivo General de Indias, Audiencia de Guadalajara 271, reels 998, 999, 1000; Reel 505, Reels 1421, 1424, 1425; Reels 511, reels 1448, 1474, 1475, 1476, undated (Box 484, Folder 2)
    - Archivo General de Indias, Audiencia de Guadalajara 272 reel 1028; 512 reels 1506, 1507, 1510, 1513, 1514, 1515, 1517, undated (Box 484, Folder 3)
    - Archivo General de Indias, Audiencia de Guadalajara 513, reels 1541, undated (Box 484, Folder 4)
    - Archivo General de Indias, Audiencia de Guadalajara 515, reels 1650, undated (Box 484, Folder 5)
    - Archivo General de Indias, Audiencia de Guadalajara 516, reels 1705, undated (Box 484, Folder 6)
    - Archivo General de Indias, Audiencia de Guadalajara 518, reels m809, 810, undated (Box 484, Folder 7)
    - Archivo General de la Nacion (Mexico) Ramo epidemias rollo 1 vols 1-2-3p, undated (Box 484, Folder 8-9)
    - Archivo General de la Nacion (Mexico) Ramo epidemias rollo 2 vol 3t-4-5p, undated (Box 484, Folder 10-11)
    - Archivo General de la Nacion (Mexico) Ramo epidemias rollo 3 vols 5t-6-7p, undated (Box 484, Folder 12-13)
    - Archivo General de la Nacion (Mexico) Ramo epidemias rollo 4 vols 7t-8, undated (Box 484, Folder 14-15)
    - Archivo General de la Nacion (Mexico) Ramo epidemias rollo 5 vols 9-10p, undated (Box 484, Folder 16-17)
    - Archivo General de la Nacion (Mexico) Ramo epidemias rollo 6 vols 10t-11-12-13p, undated (Box 484, Folder 18-19)
    - Archivo General de la Nacion (Mexico) Ramo epidemias rollo 7 vols 13t-14p, undated (Box 484, Folder 20-21)
    - Archivo General de la Nacion (Mexico) Ramo epidemias rollo 8 vols 14t-15-16-17p, undated (Box 484, Folder 22-23)
    - Archivo General de la Nacion (Mexico) Ramo epidemias rollo 9 vols 17t, undated (Box 484, Folder 24-25)
    - Archivo Historico de Hacienda Legajo 17 Las Provincias de Pimería y Sonora, undated (Box 484, Folder 26)
    - BL P.L. Pinart documents para la historia de Sonora roll 2, undated (Box 484, Folder 27)
    - BL P.L. Pinart documents para la historia de Sonora roll 3, undated (Box 484, Folder 28)
    - BL P.L. Pinart documents para la historia de Sonora roll 4, undated (Box 484, Folder 29)
    - Figueroa Expedition, undated (Box 484, Folder 30)
    - Hermosillo Cathedral Archives Rolls 1-14 Negative and Positive, undated (Box 484, Folder 31)
    - Hermosillo Cathedral Archives Rolls 15-27 Negative and Positive, undated (Box 484, Folder 32)
    - Hermosillo Cathedral Archives Rolls 28-40 Negative and Positive, undated (Box 484, Folder 33)
    - Kami (Patiño), undated (Box 484, Folder 34-35)
    - Misiones Tomo 14 1735-1796, undated (Box 484, Folder 36)
    - Papago baptisms, undated (Box 484, Folder 37)
    - Pinart Arizona published, Mexican archives, undated (Box 484, Folder 38-39)
    - Pinart Sketchbooks, undated (Box 484, Folder 40)
    - Pinart, Tradition Apache San Carlos Agency 1876 and Hehue Dialect of Opata, undated (Box 484, Folder 41)
    - Polo, Jose Toribio Apuntes sobre las epidemias en el Peru 1913, undated (Box 484, Folder 42)
- Series XIII: Oversize, 1764-1996
  This series includes oversized items from various series and subseries including Personal Files, Writings (Miscellaneous), Cornell Peru Project Files (Writings, Administrative Files and Research Data Files), Academic Files (Prescott College), Activity Files (American Society of Ethnohistory), Research Files and Photographic Material (Photograph Albums and Photographs).
  - Personal Files: Certificates, 1996 (Box 485, Folder 1)
  - Writings; Miscellaneous: Pima-Maricopa maps, undated (Box 485, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Peru Project Files; Writings: Huapra, 1960 (Box 485, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Peru Project Files; Administrative Files: Account 6274, 1964 (Box 485, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Peru Project Files; Administrative Files: Account- Morris, Earl, 1964-1965 (Box 485, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Peru Project Files; Administrative Files: AID/1a-206- Finances, 1961-1966, undated (Box 485, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Peru Project Files; Administrative Files: Cornell University Payroll Register, 1965-1966 (Box 486, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Peru Project Files; Administrative Files: NSF account 6400, 1962-1964 (Box 486, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Peru Project Files; Administrative Files: Peace Corps- Account 7504, 1963-1965 (Box 486, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Peru Project; Research Data Files: Bolivia- Corporacion Minera de Bolivia, 1964, undated (Box 487, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Peru Project; Research Data Files: Bolivia- Corporacion Minera de Bolivia, 1964, undated (Box 488, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Peru Project Files; Research Data Files: Peru- Colquiri cross tabulations, undated (Box 488, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Peru Project Files; Research Data Files: Peru- Family Life Study, 1960 (Box 488, Folder 3)
  - Academic Files; Prescott College: Kaibab- Paiute Manpower Survey- Survey data, undated (Box 488, Folder 4)
  - Activity Files; American Society of Ethnohistory: Financial ledger, 1968-1970 (Box 489, Folder 1)
  - Research Files: Archivo del Gobierno Eclesiástico de la Mitra de Sonora, Catedral de San Agustín, Rolls 1-6, 1796-1819 (Box 489, Folder 2)
  - Research Files: Archivo del Gobierno Eclesiástico de la Mitra de Sonora, Catedral de San Agustín, Rolls 7-14, 1819 (Box 489, Folder 3)
  - Research Files: Jesuit Baptism records- Caborca, Mexico, 1764 (Box 489, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Material; Photograph Albums: Chaquicocha Peru, 1964 (Box 490, Folder 1)
  - Photographic Material; Photograph Albums: Family, ca. 1943 (Box 490, Folder 2)
  - Photographic Material; Photograph Albums: High School, ca. 1940 (Box 490, Folder 3)
  - Photographic Material; Photograph Albums: High School, 1941 (Box 490, Folder 4)
  - Photographic Material; Photograph Albums: High School, 1942 (Box 490, Folder 5)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs: Kentucky, undated (Box 490, Folder 6)
  - Photographic Material; Photographs: Panoramas, undated (Box 491, Folder 1-10)